adperio.com 2019-06-15

# Revised: May 21, 2018 It is important that you fully understand what happens to the information we gather from you as

Revised: May 21, 2018
It is important that you fully understand what happens to the information we gather from you as
a publisher, advertiser or other user of Adperio’s website and services. Please read this Privacy
Statement carefully to understand how we will use and protect your personal information.
Collection of Your Personal Information
Upon registration we will ask a publisher to provide personal information such as name, email
address, physical mailing address, phone number, taxpayer ID number, or a faxed copy of a
government-issued ID. We may also collect non-personal information, such as your zip code,
the amount you spend on advertising, what type of Internet traffic you have (incentive versus
non-incentive), or the source of your Internet traffic (web versus email or search). We may use
this non-personal data to improve the services and advertising content we provide to you as well
as tailor the services provided to you. We may also share this non-personal information with
others, such as interested advertisers, in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the
information will not contain any personal information about you or any other person.
When you receive email from Adperio, we may use Web beacons and customized links (or
similar technologies) to determine whether the email has been opened and whether you clicked
on a link in the email in order to provide you more focused e-mail communications or other
information.
Other Users
For other users of the Site (non-affiliates and non-advertisers), we collect information such as IP
addresses and information regarding your browser name, the type of computer and technical
information about users’ means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system, the
Internet service providers utilized and other similar information, your mobile device type, your
device’s unique identifier and your mobile network information.
We collect personal information if you provide information such as your name, e-mail or
telephone number in the context of making an inquiry through our Site.
Use of Your Personal Information
Adperio collects and uses your personal information and other data to operate and improve our
services. These uses may include providing you with more effective affiliate management
service; making our Site easier to use; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our
services; and providing you with content and communication that are relevant to your business
objectives. More specifically, we may also use your information:
- To serve your requests and offer our services
- To improve customer service
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests, fulfill your
requests, and support needs more efficiently.
- To personalize user experience

We may use information individually or in the aggregate to understand how our users
individually or as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
- To improve our Site
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
- To send periodic emails, mailings, and contact you telephonically
We may use your contact information to respond to your inquiries, questions, and/or other
requests and to send you promotions or other offers that may be of interest to you
- To protect against certain activities
We may use your information to protect our Site, our partners and affiliates, you, other users,
and the public against potentially prohibited or illegal activities, including fraud.
- To fulfill legal requirements
We may use your information to fulfill applicable legal requirements, such as responding to
subpoenas seeking user information
- To provide targeted marketing and advertising.
We may use your information to send you marketing and advertising from us and our partners
and affiliates that we think may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive such
marketing and advertising, please see our instructions below or follow the opt-out instructions in
the marketing or advertising you receive.
- To conduct research
We may use your information to conduct research and analysis for a variety of purposes,
including to better understand our customers, to assist with our current and future service
offerings, and to understand our website visitors better.
- To manage and protect our information technology infrastructure and security
We may use your information to help manage, secure and protect our IT infrastructure and to
protect the security of our Site.
- For any other purpose with your consent
We may share with third parties the information we collect regarding IP addresses and
information regarding browser name, the type of computer and technical information about
users’ means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system, the Internet service
providers utilized and other similar information, your mobile device type, your device’s unique
identifier and your mobile network information.
We may use your information for any other purposes with your consent.
For more information about the use of information for communication, see the Communication
Preference section below.
Use of Cookies
A “cookie” is a small piece of data we store on your hard drive. When you logon to our Site
using your email address and password, we place a cookie on your hard drive. Usage of a
cookie is in no way linked to any personal information while on our site. A cookie is used for
convenience, and allows you to move from page to page of the password-protected portion of
our Site without having to login again on each page. Once you logout, these cookies are deleted

from your computer.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept
cookies, but, if you prefer, you can usually change your browser setting to decline cookies. If
you choose to decline cookies on our Site, you may still use our Site, however you may have
difficulty navigating through the password-protected portion of our Site.
Cookies are specific to the server that created them and cannot be accessed by other servers,
which means they cannot be used to track your movements around the Web.
Use of Web Beacons
Web beacons, also known as clear gifs, single-pixel gifs, pixel tags, or action tags, are tiny
electronic images that we may use in our email communication to let us know if you have
opened an email that we sent you or clicked on a link within that email.
Third Party Information Collection/”DO NOT TRACK”
With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have
relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Site. As a result of your
visit to our Site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP
address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of the
companies representing the ads or http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html.
Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on the Site or to display
advertising based upon your web browsing or application activity use Flash cookies and HTML5
to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for
removing HTML5. To manage Flash cookies, please click here:
http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.ht
ml
“Do-Not-Track” is an optional browser setting that allows you to express your preferences
regarding tracking by advertisers and other third-parties. We do not currently respond to Do-
Not-Track signals.
If you wish to limit the collection of information by us or third party partners to provide you with
advertising based upon your website browsing activities and interests, you may click
[http://preferences-mgr.truste.com] to opt out. To opt out of targeted advertising on your mobile
device, iOS users can click here: https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT205223 to learn how to
limit ad tracking and Android users can click here:
https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en to learn how to opt out of interest-based
ads. Please note that opting out of interest-based/targeted advertising does not limit all
advertising. You will continue to receive generic advertisements.
Sharing of Your Personal Information
Except as described in this statement or in any agreement that you enter with us, we will not
disclose your personal information without your consent. Adperio may disclose personal

information if required to do so by law or if we believe that such action is necessary to protect
and defend the rights, property or personal safety of Adperio and our affiliates, both publishers
and advertisers. Your personal information and other data may be transferred in connection with
a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, insolvency, or asset sale.
In order to provide our products and services, we may hire other companies to provide limited
services on our behalf, such as to send email, to perform statistical analysis of our services, to
provide affiliate support, to carry out invoicing, or to make payments. These service providers
will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to perform their functions.
They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using
it for any other purpose.
Our website contains links to the sites of third parties. When you visit these sites, please consult
those sites' individual privacy statements in order to determine how they treat user information.
Adperio is not responsible for the privacy statements or the content of such sites, and the
privacy practices of other Websites and companies are not covered by this statement. We
request that users report any and all concerns about our business partners' privacy practices
directly to us as outlined in the Contacting Us section below.
Accessing Your Personal Information
Adperio publishers are able to change their personal information at any time. The fastest way to
change personal information is to logon to your Adperio account and go to the Account Info
area, then click “Edit Account.” If for some reason this page does not work, or you have any
questions, you may contact us as outlined in the Contacting Us section below. Advertisers and
other website users may change their personal information that we collect by contacting us as
outlined in the Contacting Us section below.
Communication Preferences
If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us, you may opt out at any time.
These choices do not apply to the receipt of specific administrative notices that are required by
law, regulation, or as needed to service your account.
If you do not wish to receive email messages, you may opt out by clicking on the
“SafeUnsubscribe™” link at the bottom of any marketing email. Opt out requests made through
the “SafeUnsubscribe™” link are processed immediately.
Security
Adperio is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of
security technologies and procedures to protect your personal information from unauthorized
access, use, or disclosure. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job
are granted access to your personal information, such as our accounting department accessing
your payment information in order to send you your publisher commission payment. Our
employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desks. When

they return, they must re-enter their password to regain access.
A password is used to help protect your account and personal information. It is your
responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If
you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always logout before leaving our Site or
service to protect access to your information from subsequent users. If you feel your password
has been compromised, you should change it immediately. After you have finished using our
Site, you should logout of your Adperio account and close your browser so that no unauthorized
persons can use our Site under your name and account information.
Accountability for Onward Transfers
To effectively serve the needs of our clients, Adperio may need to share that data with certain
third parties or sub-processors. In such instances, Adperio will execute any needed contracts,
clauses or addendums to ensure that any third-party agents that it engages to process personal
data does so in a manner that is consistent with the Privacy Shield Principles. Adperio is
potentially liable for onward transfers to third parties of personal data of EU individuals received
pursuant to Privacy Shield.
Jurisdiction
Adperio has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield
Principles. Adperio states that if there is any conflict between the terms of our privacy policy and
the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. Adperio is also subject
to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC). To
learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view Adperio’s Privacy Shield certification,
please visit www.privacyshield.gov.
Changes to This Privacy Statement
We will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect changes in our services. When we
post changes to this Statement, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this
statement. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how
Adperio is using and protecting your information.
Recourse & Enforcement
In instances where other redress possibilities have been exhausted under EU law, or where the
complaint has not been resolved by any other means, EU end users may be entitled to invoke
binding arbitration option before the Privacy Shield Panel. Adperio acknowledges that any final
decision by the Privacy Shield Panel is a legally binding decision, enforceable in US courts.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions or concerns about your privacy at Adperio, please contact us by
clicking here, or you may contact us in writing at:

Adperio
Attn: Privacy Department
2000 S. Colorado Blvd. Tower 1
Suite 7000
Denver, CO 80222
